[Music]
This information is only our opinion and
not financial advice. Please do your own research before making any decision.
We are not responsible for any profit or loss.
Hello Viewers,
today's update on Foreign Investor Deals is like this:
1 million shares of Bodhi Tree Multimedia Ltd. were bought by Central Securities India
Markets Pvt Ltd at a price of ₹1.18 per
share. These shares belong to the
Trader Public category. Bought by Vikas Kumar Verma Hoff.
This was today's bulk deals. Let's take a look at
today's blog deals on ICICI
Lord General Insurance Company Limited.
Total shares of the company 200 K were
bought by Aditya Bela Sun Life Mutual Fund which belongs to the
Trader Public category.
Total shares of ICICI Lord General Insurance Company Limited 75 K were bought
by Black Stone Aqua Master Sub Fund which belongs
to the Trader Public category.
Total shares of the company 225 K were
bought by Goldman Sachs Singapore Private Limited.
ICICI Lord General
Insurance Company Limited belongs to the Trader Public category. The total shares of the company were
100% which were bought by Morgan Stanley Asia
Singapore Private Limited.
ICICI Lord General Insurance Company
Limited belongs to the Trader Public category. The total shares of the company were 110% which were
bought by Societe Generale.
Thank you for watching today's major foreign investors deals. Subscribe to the channel for stock latest news updates
and
like and share the video.